U.S. President's Railroad Commission Photographs 5003 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI: Chicago River and Indiana Railroad: Chicago Industries and Union Stock Yards
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 161)
    Shows switching movements at the Hygrade Packing Plant at 3900 South Emerald Avenue. As you can see from the picture, Emerald Avenue is a through street and traffic is very heavy. All signals are on the fireman's side. Notice in the picture how close the automobile traffic moves to the train.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 161)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 162)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 162)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 163)
    Taken in and around the Hygrade Plant. It shows a switching operation at the plant. The signals are passed on the fireman's side.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 163)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 164)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 164)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 165)
    Shows a switch being made at the inside track of the Hygrade Plant. Observe how the brakeman is working on the left side of the engine and will have to give the signal to the fireman. Note also the automobile parked between the two tracks. Over on the right are two automobiles are sandwiched between the boxer and the tank-car in the rear. Notice also in the rear of the picture the automobile which is crossing the tracks just behind the car which is being coupled.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 165)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 166)
    Switching operation at Hygrade Plant on South Emerald Avenue, fireman's side.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 166)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 167)
    Shows another view around the Hygrade Plant. Again notice how the tracks cross the public street, the pedestrian traffic in and around the plant and the passenger cars, which pass very close to the tracks.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 167)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 168a)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 168a)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 168b)
    Shows the switching operation in progress at the Hygrade Packing Plant. notice how the tracks head across the public streets. Notice also the very heavy volume of traffic and the large number of pedestrians working around the tracks on both sides of the street.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 168b)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 169)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 169)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 170)
    Switching operation at plant. Notice how close tracks are to public street. Wider view of clearance at same curve as seen in exhibit K-10.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 170)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 171)
    The train is coming out of the Hygrade Plant. Traffic is going south on a one-way street. Again, due to curvature of the track, the traffic, going south on the street, can be viewed only by the fireman as the engineer's view is cut off.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 171)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant and Manhattan Brewery, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 172)
    Shows Hygrade Plant on the right and Manhattan Brewing on the left. Signals are taken on fireman's side at both locations. Because of close clearances and parked automobiles, sharp lookout must be maintained on both sides of the locomotive.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 172)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 173)
    Shows a car being set out near the Hygrade Plant. The brakeman is working on the fireman's side of the engine. Notice how he is giving the signal.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 173)
  - Hygrade Meat Plant and Surrounding Streets, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 174)
    CRI Unit #9811. Shows an overall view of the Hygrade Plant and the surrounding streets. An automobile in the foreground is parked close to the tracks. There is also a heavy volume of traffic on the street. The traffic shown in the picture can only be seen by the fireman. Notice also the congestion around the tracks shown over to the right where the jeep is working right on the tracks. Also notice how the signals are being given on the fireman's side. It is impossible to give signals on the engineer's side due to the curvature of the track. There is no protection at this crossing other than the cross-arm sign.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 174)
  - Fireman taking signals, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 175)
    Taken out of the back window of the cab of the locomotive and shows the fireman taking signals at the 40th and Wallace crossing over two main line tracks. It is apparent from the picture that the engineer would be unable to see the man giving the signals.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 175)
  - Fireman taking signals, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 176)
    Taken out back window of locomotive. Another view at the 40th and Normal Avenue crossing. The fireman is watching for the clearance of cars and is also watching out for the safety of any pedestrians who might be in the area.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 176)
  - Fireman taking signals, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 177)
    We see the fireman taking signals at the 40th and Wallace crossing while the switchman is throwing the switch. Again it is obvious, form the curvature of the track, that the engineer would be unable to see the switchman.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 56, Folder 177)
- Series VII: Denver's Burnham Yards: The Rio Grande (DRGW), Colorado & Southern, and Santa Fe Railway (ATSF) facilities
  This series consists of photographs of the facilities in Denver, Colorado's Burnham Yards. These photographs were not submitted to the Commission and as such do not have identifying exhibit numbers. These photographs document railroad facilities in and around Denver, Colorado. This includes industries around Cherry Creek, the Rio Grande's Car Shops and Freight Yards, AT&SF Yards, Denver Union Station and its passenger Yards, and grade crossings in industrial areas. Because these photographs were not used before the Commission, there is limited descriptive data for some of the images. As the Burnham Shops and Yards were the hub of the Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad, it is likely that these photographs were taken by one of its employees. The D&RGW was a class I railroad operating in the western United States between Colorado and California.
  - Burnham Car Shops, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    Car shop and passenger cars on tracks.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Burnham Car Shops, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 116)
    Freight cars, gondolas and tank car in picture as well.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 116)
  - Downtown Denver Industry Sidings, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 117)
    1500 block of Wykoop Street, downtown Denver. Railroad tracks running next to loading platforms and loading docks.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 117)
  - Freight Houses, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 118)
    Freight cars on tracks next to loading platforms.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 118)
  - Grade Crossing Over Tracks, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 119)
    Freight houses to right of frame.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 119)
  - D&RGW Railroad Tracks, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 120)
    Bridge over Cherry Creek, downtown Denver, between 14th and 16th Streets.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 120)
  - Burnham Yard Shops, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 146)
    D&RGW Unit #5651; D&RGW Unit #74. Tracks leading to car shop and turntable
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 146)
  - Burnham Yard tracks, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 147)
    These are tracks of the Denver Rio Grande Western Railroad at Burnam Yard in Denver.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 147)
  - Burnham Car Shops and Freight Yard, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 148)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 148)
  - Burnham Car Shops, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 149)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 149)
  - Burnham Car Shops, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 150)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 150)
  - Burnham Car Shops, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 151)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 151)
  - Grade Crossing Over Tracks, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 152)
    Location in downtown Denver.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 152)
  - Burnham Car Shops, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 153)
    Tank cars in foreground are not on tracks.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 153)
  - Burnham Yards, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 154)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 154)
  - Grade Crossing, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 155)
    Corner of Market and 21st Street, in downtown Denver.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 155)
  - Grade Crossing, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 156)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 156)
  - D&RGW Railroad Tracks, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 157)
    Bridge over Cherry Creek, downtown Denver
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 157)
  - D&RGW Railroad Tracks, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 158)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 158)
  - D&RGW Railroad Tracks, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 159)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 159)
  - Downtown Denver Industry Sidings, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 160)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 160)
  - Industrial Siding, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 161)
    Location probably in downtown Denver.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 161)
  - Denver Union Station Team tracks: CB&Q, C&S, AT&SF, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 162)
    Looking at freight cars, tank cars, and hopper cars on tracks towards Union Station. Passenger cars are in the background.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 162)
  - Burham Shops and Roundhouse, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 163)
    DRGW Unit #5651; Burnham Yard Shops and turntable.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 163)
  - Rio Grande Mechanical Department, Burnham Shops, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 164)
    Empire Gas and Electric Equipment industry in right of photograph.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 164)
  - Grade Crossing Over Empty Railroad Tracks, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 165)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 165)
  - Rio Grande Mechanical Department, Burnham Shops, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 166)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 63, Folder 166)
- Series VIII: Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railway: mining and shipping operations
  This series consists of photographs of the Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railway's facilities in Minnesota. These photographs were not submitted to the Commission and as such do not have identifying exhibit numbers. The Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railway is a railroad operating in northern Minnesota and Wisconsin that hauled iron ore and later taconite to the Great Lakes ports of Duluth and Two Harbors, Minnesota. The photographs document the trackage, viaducts, ore docks, ships, coal yards, and carrier facilities as well as extensive documentation from inside the locomotive cab of a DM&IR train hauling coal hoppers. The viaducts and ore docks are located in either Duluth or Two Harbors, Minnesota The train yards are most likely in Proctor, Minnesota; other locations are unidentified. Because these photographs were not used before the Commission, there is limited descriptive data for some of the images.
  - Ore Train in Open Pit Mine Switching Locomotive and Slug (Box 59, Folder 97)
    DMIR Unit #1204
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 97)
  - Open Pit Mine and Ore Cars (Box 59, Folder 98)
    DMIR Units 1204 and 1206
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 98)
  - Open Pit Mine and Ore Cars (Box 59, Folder 99)
    DMIR Unit 1202
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 99)
  - Open Pit Mine (Box 59, Folder 100)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 100)
  - Open Pit Mine (Box 59, Folder 101)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 101)
  - Open Pit Mine (Box 59, Folder 102)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 102)
  - Open Pit Mine with Ore Train and Slug (Box 59, Folder 103)
    DMIR Unit 1205
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 103)
  - Ore Trains in Pit Mine (Box 59, Folder 104)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 104)
  - Open Pit Mine (Box 59, Folder 105)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 105)
  - Ore Cars and Ore Train (Box 59, Folder 106)
    DMIR Ore Cars 33060 and 27072. Ore train and slug in background.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 106)
  - Ore Cars on Pier (Box 59, Folder 107)
    On viaduct to loading docks and container ships.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 107)
  - Ore Cars on Pier (Box 59, Folder 108)
    On viaduct to loading docks and container ships. Cab view from engineer's side on approach to the ore dock
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 108)
  - Ore Cars on Viaduct (Box 59, Folder 109)
    DMIR Unit 180 (manufacturer: EMD model: SD 18) with ship, the U.S.S. Elbert H. Gary.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 109)
  - Ore Cars on Pier (Box 59, Folder 110)
    On viaduct to loading docks and container ships. Cab view from fireman's side on approach to the ore dock.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 110)
  - Ore Cars on Pier (Box 59, Folder 111)
    On viaduct. View from fireman's side of the cab.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 111)
  - Ore Cars on Pier (Box 59, Folder 112)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 112)
  - View of Locomotive and Ore Train from Fireman's Side (Box 59, Folder 113)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 113)
  - View Out of Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 59, Folder 114)
    DMIR caboose.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 114)
  - View Out of Engineer's Side of Cab (Box 59, Folder 115)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 115)
  - View Out of Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 59, Folder 116)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 116)
  - View Out of Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 59, Folder 117)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 117)
  - Track Speeder (Box 59, Folder 118)
    Maintenance of Way worker.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 118)
  - Track Speeder (Box 59, Folder 119)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 119)
  - Track Speeder (Box 59, Folder 120)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 120)
  - Track Speeder (Box 59, Folder 121)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 121)
  - Railroad Tracks and Grade Crossing (Box 59, Folder 122)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 122)
  - View of Ore Train from Engineer's Side (Box 59, Folder 123)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 123)
  - View from Fireman's Side of Locomotive (Box 59, Folder 124)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 124)
  - DMIR Unit 159 with Gondola (Box 59, Folder 125)
    Manufacturer: EMD Model: SD 9
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 125)
  - Ore Cars and Ore Dock Seen From Cab (Box 59, Folder 126)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 126)
  - Ore Cars in Yard Seen From Cab (Box 59, Folder 127)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 127)
  - Ore Cars and Ore Dock Seen From Cab (Box 59, Folder 128)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 128)
  - Ore Cars on Pier (Box 59, Folder 129)
    View out of fireman's side of cab. Photograph labeled "End of Block."
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 129)
  - Locomotive Cab: Fireman's Side (Box 59, Folder 130)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 130)
  - Flat Car and Ore Train (Box 59, Folder 132)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 132)
  - View of Fireman's Side of Locomotive and Ore Train (Box 59, Folder 133)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 133)
  - View of Ore Train from Engineer's Side (Box 59, Folder 134)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 134)
  - View of Ore Train from Engineer's Side (Box 59, Folder 135)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 135)
  - Viaduct to Ore Dock (Box 59, Folder 136)
    DMIR Unit 180, Manufacturer: EMD Model: SD 18, with ore cars.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 136)
  - Viaduct to Ore Dock (Box 59, Folder 137)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 137)
  - Ore Cars in Yard (Box 59, Folder 138)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 138)
  - View Out of Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 59, Folder 139)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 139)
  - View from Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 59, Folder 140)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 140)
  - Viaduct to Ore Dock (Box 59, Folder 141)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 141)
  - Ore Cars in Yard (Box 59, Folder 142)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 142)
  - Ore Cars on Viaduct (Box 59, Folder 143)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 143)
  - Railroad Tracks on Viaduct (Box 59, Folder 144)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 144)
  - Railroad Tracks on Viaduct (Box 59, Folder 145)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 145)
  - View Out of Engineer's Side of Locomotive (Box 59, Folder 146)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 146)
  - View from Locomotive Approaching Ore Dock (Box 59, Folder 147)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 147)
  - Ore Train on Viaduct (Box 59, Folder 148)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 148)
  - Ore Train on Viaduct (Box 59, Folder 149)
    View from fireman's side of locomotive.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 149)
  - View from Engineer's Side of Cab on Viaduct (Box 59, Folder 150)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 150)
  - View from Engineer's Side of Cab (Box 59, Folder 151)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 151)
  - Duluth Missabe and Iron Range Ore Train (Box 59, Folder 152)
    Unknown Locomotive.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 152)
  - Cab View from Fireman's Side (Box 59, Folder 153)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 153)
  - View from Engineer's Side of Cab (Box 59, Folder 154)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 59, Folder 154)
  - View from Fireman's Side (Box 60, Folder 38)
    Duluth RR (see box 59, f 114)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Ore Cars and Railroad Track Crossovers (Box 60, Folder 39)
    Full ore cars in background.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Track Speeder (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Track Speeder (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - View of Ore Cars from Fireman's Side of Locomotive (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - DMIR Unit 180 on Viaduct (Box 60, Folder 43)
    Manufacturer: EMD Model: SD 18
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - Open Pit Mine (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 44)
  - Flat Car and Ore Train (Box 60, Folder 45)
    Approaching viaduct and ore docks. DMIR Caboose C-161.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - View from Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 46)
  - Duluth Missabe and Iron Range Ore Train (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 47)
  - View of Ore Cars from Fireman's Side (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 48)
  - Ore Train on Viaduct (Box 60, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 49)
  - View of Fireman's Side of Locomotive and Ore Train (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 50)
  - View of Engineer's Side of Locomotive Cab (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 51)
  - Fireman's Side of Ore Train (Box 60, Folder 52)
    Big container ships at ore dock.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 52)
  - Viaduct and Ore Cars (Box 60, Folder 53)
    DM&IR Unit 123 pulling a caboose with employees riding on the back.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 53)
  - DMIR Unit 180 on Viaduct to Ore Dock (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 54)
  - View of Locomotive and Ore Train from Fireman's Side (Box 60, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 55)
  - Ore Cars and Ore Train (Box 60, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 56)
  - View from Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 60, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 57)
  - DMIR Unit 159 with Gondola (Box 60, Folder 58)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 58)
  - Grade Crossing Over Tracks (Box 60, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 59)
  - Ore Train on Fireman's Side (Box 60, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 60)
  - Ore Train and Ore Cars on Tracks (Box 60, Folder 61)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 61)
  - Ore Cars (Box 60, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 62)
  - Track Speeder (Box 60, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 63)
  - Grade Crossing Over Tracks (Box 60, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 64)
  - Ore Train on Viaduct (Box 60, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 65)
  - Ore Cars and Ore Train on Viaduct from Fireman's Side (Box 60, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 66)
  - View from Engineer's Side of Cab (Box 60, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 67)
  - Ore Cars in Yard Seen From Cab (Box 60, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 68)
  - View from Engineer's Side of Cab (Box 60, Folder 69)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 69)
  - View of Ore Cars on Viaduct (Box 60, Folder 70)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 70)
  - View from Fireman's Side of Cab of Oncoming Ore Train (Box 60, Folder 71)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 71)
  - Duluth Missabe and Iron Range Unit 159 (Box 60, Folder 72)
    Manufacturer: EMD Model: SD 9.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 72)
  - Track Speeder and Grade Crossing Over Tracks (Box 60, Folder 73)
    Maintenance of Way employee.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 73)
  - View from Fireman's Side of Ore Train (Box 60, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 74)
  - Ore Cars on Tracks (Box 60, Folder 75)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 75)
  - Engineer's Side of Ore Train on Viaduct (Box 60, Folder 76)
    Taken from cab of DMIR Unit 180.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 76)
  - Engineer's Side of Locomotive from Cab (Box 60, Folder 77)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 77)
  - View from Engineer's Side of Cab (Box 60, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 78)
  - Open Pit Mine and Railroad Tracks (Box 60, Folder 79)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 79)
  - Track Speeder and Grade Crossings Over Tracks (Box 60, Folder 80)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 80)
  - View from Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 60, Folder 81)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 81)
  - View of Ore Cars from Fireman's Side of Locomotive (Box 60, Folder 82)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 82)
  - Ore Cars on Tracks and Railroad Crossovers (Box 60, Folder 83)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 83)
  - View Out of Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 60, Folder 84)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 84)
  - View of Ore Cars from Fireman's Side of Cab (Box 60, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 85)
  - Ore Cars from Fireman's Side of Locomotive (Box 60, Folder 86)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 86)